ALLEN DIWAN: Hi.
My name is Allen Diwan.
I'm the owner and chef of Kashmir Indian Restaurant in Budapest.
The dish now we're going to be preparing is called paneer masala.
One ingredient that we'll be adding also is the tomatoes whilst the ginger and the garlic have been cooked slightly.
So, just--we'll give it one more shake, stir it once more properly.
The onions have been slightly browned now, and we added our green ginger, garlic, and the chilies.
We'll wait for that to cook and in the meanwhile, we'll take our tomatoes, maybe about 3 of them, and we'll cut them into cubes.
Again, we do not want tomatoes to be cut into very small cubes because we want to see, I mean, obviously, it will be cooked well with the masala, but you'll somehow see the redness of the tomato.
And it's also, cooking the food is also about seeing the color of the food in the dish.
You'll see the different flavors.
You'll see the different ingredients that we are going to put in this dish that you see the unique--the ingre--the colors of each and every ingredient, and this is part of the appeal.
I might add one more tomato of this dish, that you can see it's very rustic and you have to make it appetizing for--'cause you eat with your eyes as well, and you want to make this dish as appetizing as possible.
So, this is quite a straight forward recipe, and the ginger, garlic, we're waiting for the ginger to cook properly.
And for 1 more 2--1 or 2 more minutes, we'll give it--we'll leave it for 1 or 2 more minutes, and then we'll add our tomatoes to this.